JACK GILBERT

CONTACT

(952) 215-5879 jackwgilbert00@gmail.com

EDUCATION

University of Wisconsin - Stout September 2018 to Present

- B.F.A. in Graphic Design and Interactive Media
- Minor in Computer Science

SKILLS

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe XD
- Adobe Dreamweaver
- Jira
- DevTrack
- Video Technologies
- Technical Troubleshooting
- Design Drawing
- Illustration
- Javascript
- HTML5
- CSS
- PHP
- C++
- C#

PROFILE

A designer that's proven to be an incredibly quick learner with an excellent work ethic. Experienced in troubleshooting technical equipment, utilizing design technologies as well as leading teams during large projects. Currently pursuing a career in Graphic Design with a focus in Interactive Media and is a proud member of the LGBT+ community.

EXPERIENCE

Video Technician

UW-Stout | January 2019 - Present

- Lead a team for video technologies on large events.
- Directed camera shots and angles.
- Experience troubleshooting event technology.
- Ran events independently and provided technical support.

Web Development Director

Blue Devil Productions | January 2020 - January 2021

- Directed a website for event planning and promotion.
- Maintained and managed the website.
- Created microsites for specialized events.
- Redesigned aspects of the main website.

Functional Tester

Activision | May 2019 - August 2019 / May 2021 - August 2021

- Tested functionality for triple A video game releases.
- Credited in multiple Call of Duty titles.
- Experience troubleshooting video game technologies.
- A top monthly bug writer while employed.

Barista

Starbucks | June 2016 - August 2018

- Provided excellent customer servies for a large coffee chain.
- Ran front of house and crafted complex beverages.
- Registered trainer for new baristas.